## Jörg Bernhard Reske

Tel.: (+5584) 99968-5830 Email: jorg.reske@gmail.com

# Product Management • UX Design • Software Engineering • Software Application Developer

Analytical, innovative software development professional with extensive experience in evaluating, executing and deploying systems, improving quality and efficiency. Adept at aligning end-user needs with complex IT solutions. Skilled troubleshooter, continually focused on identifying, isolating, and resolving technical issues. Strong business acumen, accomplished in functional and technical analysis, design and documentation. Exceptional communicator, skilled in building effective cross-team collaborations and strengthening relationships across functions to drive cohesive, technical operations. Extensive teaching experience.

#### CAREER ACCOMPLISHMENTS

210 MW windfarm in successful operation, and another 800 MW registered and under development all over the country. Specialist to prepare and adapt wind plant projects for auction, construction, and operation in full compliancy with Brazilian regulations. Created for Acera a significant pipline of projects under development, and contracted areas totaling 10.000, ha in the South of Brazil, as well as 3.500, ha in the NE. Those are the most promising regions for wind power in Brazil. Developed and marked a network for ATT to establish cellular connections all over the continent. Connected TTI (Hellmann) international to all branches all over the South America. Developed e warehous for TKS inthe name of Garoto, capacity of 10650 pallets, fully automatic, 7 trans-elevators, top security sprinkler system.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

General Manager 2009 - 2022

Acera Consulting Services, a successful consulting firm. Integrated agile and traditional methodologies into software engineering and development processes for various companies.

IT Manager for South America 2007 - 2009

IT Network Services, successful construction of IT network to distant windfarms.

General Manager Siah 2002 - 2007

General Manager structuring sales organization. inhouse IT structuring, Servers Net and "WiFi networks".

Elaboration of projects for Desbravador.

General Manager Hotel Rosa Nautica 2001 - 2007

Basic Hotel Management, structuring, organization and Finance organization.

Project Manager TTI 1998 - 2001Project Manager, IT - implementation, introduction of ISO 9002.

Project Manager ATT USA 1997 – 1998 Wireless Project development for ATT - Desert of Maricopa Arizona USA.

Project Manager Assistant 1993 - 1997 Project Coordination;

### **EDUCATION**

University Köln Administration Management; Humboldt Tecnical School International Trade Management; PCD Web-Design; CubosAcademy Fullstack Engineer; UX UI Web-Design;

#### **LANGUAGES**

German • Native English • almost native Portuguese • almost native Spanish • basic